Guide to the Stanford University, Vice President for Business Affairs, Records
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Roads - Streets & Walks - Traffic Signals, 1956-1973 (Box 57, Folder 5)
- Roads - Walsh Road Abandonment, 1961 (Box 47, Folder 8)
- Roads - West Fremont Avenue Abandonment, 1962-1964 (Box 47, Folder 9)
- Roads - Whiskey Hill Road, 1951-1952 (Box 57, Folder 1)
- Roads - Willow Freeway / Expressway II, 1962-1967 (Box 47, Folder 11)
- Roads - Willow Freeway / Expressway, 1934-1962 (Box 47, Folder 10)
- Roads - Willow Freeway Extension - Stanford case for Sand Hill Road alignment rather than Alpine Road alignment, 1964 (Box 65, Folder 17)
- Roads - Willow Freeway/ Expressway, III, 1968-1970 (Box 57, Folder 3)
- Roads - Willow Freeway/Expressway - Newwspaper Clippings, 1966-1974 (Box 57, Folder 4)
- Roads - Willow Road Committee Minutes, 1967-1970 (Box 57, Folder 2)
- Roads and Streets - Reports and Recommendations, 1949-1950 (Box 47, Folder 5)
- Roads, Streets and Walks - II, 1957-1964 (Box 47, Folder 6)
- Roads, Streets and Walks, 1963-1967 (Box 47, Folder 7)
- Robinson, I. N. Jr., 1944-1955 (Box 47, Folder 12)
- Roble Hall, 1974 Plumbing Renovations (incl. budget), File 1, 883, 1974-1975 (Box 109, Folder 3)
- Rogers, A. F. and Carolyn H., 1934-1958 (Box 47, Folder 18)
- Roggeveen, Vincent J., 1959-1963 (Box 47, Folder 13)
- Rogow, Arnold A.- (593 Alvarado), 1963-1966 (Box 47, Folder 15)
- Rogow, Arnold A., 1959-1963 (Box 47, Folder 14)
- Roos Brothers, INC.- Campus, 1936-1959 (Box 47, Folder 16)
- Rowell Property - Belmont, 1951-1954 (Box 47, Folder 17)
- RRA Chronological File, 1976 (Box 93, Folder 1)
- RRA Chronological File, 1976 (Box 93, Folder 3)
- RRA's Chronological File, 1977 (Box 92, Folder 11)
- Rudge, WM. E. Printing House, 1930 (Box 47, Folder 19)
- Russel, Mrs. Theresa (Miss Buckingham), 1936 (Box 47, Folder 20)
- Russell, Robert D., 1961-1965 (Box 47, Folder 21)
- S. F. Post - Fire House Studies, 1966-1968 (Box 27, Folder 12)
- S.U. Medical Center Hospital Expansion Phase I - CMCS Monthly Report, 1973 (Binder) (Box 35)
- Safe Deposit Vault - Wells Fargo Bank, Palo Alto, Calif., 1955-1974 (Box 57, Folder 6)
- Safekeeping of Records, see: Security - Safekeeping of Records (Box 57, Folder 7)
- Safety, Insurance & Health - Exhibits (Box 57, Folder 15)
- Safety, Insurance & Health - General, 1966-1970 (Box 57, Folder 8)
- Safety, Insurance & Health - Health (Health & Safety Inspections of all Univ. Food & Hsng. Units, inc. Fraternities), 1967-1974 (Box 57, Folder 9)
- Safety, Insurance & Health - Health Physics & Indust. Hygiene, 2, 1966-1973 (Box 57, Folder 11)
- Safety, Insurance & Health - Health, 1965-1974 (Box 57, Folder 10)
- Safety, Insurance & Health - OSHA, R-8104, Case 13 - University, 1954-1974 (Box 57, Folder 12)
- Safety, Insurance & Health - OSHA, R-8104, Case 14 - Hospital, 1973-1974 (Box 57, Folder 13)
- Safety, Insurance & Health - Safety, 1965-1972 (Box 57, Folder 14)
- Safety, Insurance and Health -Insurance, 1965 -1973 (Box 47, Folder 23)
- Safety, Insurance and Health - “Public Health and Safety”, 1958-1963 (Box 47, Folder 24)
- Safety, Insurance and Health - Health Physics and Indust. Hygiene, 1965-1966 (Box 47, Folder 22)
- Saks Fifth Avenue - Site Development (Plans) (Box 48, Folder 2)
- Saks Fifth Avenue - Site Development Construction, 1960-1964 (Box 48, Folder 1)
- Sales Volume Reports, 1975-1978 (Box 35, Folder 1)
- Salvatierra - 517 (Former Weymouth House), 1951-1959 (Box 48, Folder 4)
- Salvatierra - 521 (University Owned), 1943- 1959 (Box 48, Folder 3)
- Salvatierra - 523 (University Owned), 1943-1963 (Box 48, Folder 12)
- Salvatierra - 525 (University Owned), 1950-1963 (Box 48, Folder 7)
- Salvatierra - 534, 1964 (Box 48, Folder 8)
- Salvatierra - 535 (University Owned), The Elms (Box 48, Folder 9)
- Salvatierra - 541 (University Owned), 1963-1966 (Box 48, Folder 5)
- Salvatierra - 549 (University Owned), Rogers House, 1955-1964 (Box 48, Folder 10)
- Salvatierra - 553 (University Owned), Owen and Hawthorne (Psychology Research) (Box 48, Folder 11)
- Salvatierra - 568 (University Owned), 1963 (Box 48, Folder 6)
- Salvatierra - 575 (Huston House) - University Owned, 1966 (Box 57, Folder 16)
- San Bernardino County Property, 1953-1957 (Box 48, Folder 13)
- San Francisco - 440 Montgomery St. Property (Miss F. Olga Meyer, Mrs. A. Meyer Buck), 1961-1962 (Box 48, Folder 18)
- San Francisco County - Lowry Property, San Francisco, CA, 1958 (Box 48, Folder 15)
- San Francisco County Property, SOLD, 1958-1962 (Box 48, Folder 14)
- San Francisco Water Company - Correspondence, Folder I, 1960-1962 (Box 48, Folder 21)
- San Francisco Water Company - Correspondence, Folder II, 1962-1974 (Box 57, Folder 19)
- San Francisco Water Company - Miscellaneous (Box 57, Folder 20)
- San Francisco Water Company, 1948-1950 (Box 48, Folder 19)
- San Francisco Water Company, 1950-1953 (Box 48, Folder 20)
- San Francisco Water Division - Right of Way, 1938 (Box 48, Folder 22)
- San Francisco, City and County of - Hospital Care for Indigent (Outpatient), 1955-1960 (Box 48, Folder 17)
- San Francisco, City and County of - Hospital Care for Indigent Sick (Inpatient), 1948-1959 (Box 48, Folder 16)
- San Francisquito Creek Dam - Folder #6, 1968-1969 (Box 49, Folder 1)
- San Francisquito Creek Dam, Folder 1, 1950-1957 (Box 48, Folder 23)
- San Francisquito Creek Dam, Folder 2 (see also: Water, El Camino Widening, Sewers, City of P. A., Lake Lagunita), 1957-1961 (Box 48, Folder 24)
- San Francisquito Creek Dam, Folder 3, (see also: above, Mr. Post’s water reports) 1961-1963 (Box 48, Folder 25)
- San Francisquito Creek Dam, Folder 4, (see also: above, Mr. Post’s water reports), 1963-1965 (Box 48, Folder 26)
- San Francisquito Creek Dam, Folder 5, (see also: above, Mr. Post’s water reports), 1965-1967 (Box 48, Folder 27)
- San Jose Chamber of Commerce Industrial Committee, 1954-1957 (Box 49, Folder 2)
- San Mateo County - Gift from Milton Meyer Foundation - Hillborough, California, 1964 (Box 49, Folder 4)
- San Mateo County Property - Reppas, Geo. S., 1963 (Box 49, Folder 3)
- Sand Hill Road Association, 1967-1969 (Box 57, Folder 17)
- Sands, Maurice - Agreement, 1961 (Box 57, Folder 18)
- Sansom, Sir George and Lady Katherine, 1956-1965 (Box 49, Folder 5)
- Santa Clara Co. Joint Housing Element - Frenchman’s Terrace, 1971 (Box 95, Folder 24)
- Santa Clara County - Exhibits (Box 57, Folder 21)
- Santa Clara County Sheriff’s Agreement, 1968-1971 (Box 57, Folder 22)
- Santa Clara Property (Estate of Arlene Z. Hand) - San Jose, California, 1961-1962 (Box 49, Folder 6)
- Santa Cruz County, California - Charles E. Uhl Property, 1958-1964 (Box 49, Folder 7)
- Santa Margarita Ranch - Coldwell, Banker Appraisal, 1970 (Binder) (Box 73)
- Santa Margarita Ranch - RRA, 1971-1973 (Box 72, Folder 13)
- Santa Teresa - 418 - University Owned, 1957-1962 (Box 57, Folder 23)
- Sarpa, Emil J., 1972-1978 (Box 73, Folder 31)
- SAS User's Guide (Binder) (Box 73)
- Sather, Otis H., 1948-1960 (Box 49, Folder 8)
- Scarf, Herbert E., 1961-1963 (Box 49, Folder 9)
- Schaeffer, Albert C., 1946-1947 (Box 49, Folder 10)
- Schiller, Anna Maria, 1943 (Box 49, Folder 11)
- Schneider, Edward J., 1945 (Box 49, Folder 12)
- School of Education - Alterations for Lounge #1, 721, 1972-1975 (Box 103, Folder 16)
- School of Education Lounge - Landscape Work #2, 721, 1973-1974 (Box 103, Folder 20)
- Schools - Frenchman’s Terrace, 1971-1972 (Box 95, Folder 25)
- Schools - Las Lomitas School District - Exhibits (Box 57, Folder 25)
- Schools - Las Lomitas School District, 1955-1967 (Box 57, Folder 24)
- Schools - Palo Alto Unified School District - Lots 44 & 45, 1955-1965 (Box 58, Folder 2)
- Schools - Palo Alto Unified School District - Proposed School Sites, 1953-1971 (Box 58, Folder 3)
- Schools - Palo Alto Unified School District - Stanford Elementary School #2, 1963-1971 (Box 58, Folder 1)
- Schools - Palo Alto Unified School District Building Advisory Committee, 1954-1957 (Box 57, Folder 26)
- Schools - Portola Valley School District, 1957-1959 (Box 58, Folder 4)
- Schools- San Mateo Junior College, 1961 (Box 49, Folder 13)
- Schultz, E. W. and Francel R., 1957-1965 (Box 49, Folder 14)
- SCIP - Encina Rms 30 & 40 Alterations, 879, 1974-1975 (Box 109, Folder 4)
- SCIP [Stanford Center for Information Processing], 786, 1972-1975 (Box 109, Folder 18)
- SCIP Encina Basement Alterations, (943), 1975 (Box 108, Folder 19)
- SCIP Programs - FPCU & Land Res., 1977-1978 (Box 33, Folder 29)
- SCIP, 1970-1975 (Box 100, Folder 6)
- SCIP, 786, 1973-1974 (Box 109, Folder 19)
- Servadyne Corporation - Air Engineering, 1964-1965 (Box 115, Folder 16)
- Service Yard Building 550 - General, Legal Documents, 173C, 1963-1964 (Box 102, Folder 10)
- Sewall, Dr. Edward C., 1933-1959 (Box 49, Folder 15)
- Sewer, 1953 (Box 49, Folder 19)
- Sewers - (R.C. Johnston's file), 1954-1959 (Box 49, Folder 16)
- Sewers - Arastradero Road Sewer Line, 1960-1964 (Box 58, Folder 11)
- Sewers - Foothills Area, 1965-1966 (Box 58, Folder 12)
- Sewers - Ladera, 1951-1961 (Box 58, Folder 13)
- Sewers - Menlo Park Sanitary Dist., Folder 1 of 2 - Reports and Maps (Box 58, Folder 7)
- Sewers - Menlo Park Sanitary Dist., Folder 2 of 2 - Reports and Maps (Box 58, Folder 6)
- Sewers - Menlo Park Sanitary District - Correspondence and Documents, 1958-1968 (Box 58, Folder 14)
- Sewers - Palo Alto, City of - 1. Correspondence, 1946-1955 (Box 49, Folder 21)
- Sewers - Palo Alto, City of - 2. Correspondence, 1955-1965 (Box 49, Folder 22)
- Sewers - Palo Alto, City of - 3. Correspondence, 1965-1971 (Box 49, Folder 23)
- Sewers - Palo Alto, City of - Correspondence, 1971-1973 (Box 58, Folder 15)
- Sewers - Palo Alto, City of - Documents, 1955-1971 (Box 58, Folder 8)
- Sewers - Palo Alto, City of - East Trunk Line, 1957 (Box 58, Folder 9)
- Sewers - Palo Alto, City of - West Trunk Line, 1966-1973 (Box 58, Folder 10)
- Sewers - Proposed Sewerage System for Stanford Lands, 1955 (Box 58, Folder 16)
- Sewers - Residential Area - Sewage Disposal System (With Menlo Investment) Proposed, 1952 (Box 49, Folder 17)
- Sewers, 1948-1971 (Box 58, Folder 5)
- Sewers, 1950-1958 (Box 49, Folder 18)
- Shaw Loomis and Sayles, 1928-1929 (Box 49, Folder 24)
- Shedd, Jeannette Bell - Memorial Fund, 1939-1940 (Box 49, Folder 25)
- Shedd, Solon, 1940 (Box 49, Folder 26)
- Shell Oil Company - Campus Service Station (old location), 1940-1961 (Box 49, Folder 28)
- Shell Oil Company - Highway Service Station, 1941-1961 (Box 49, Folder 29)
- Shell Oil Company, 1929-1937 (Box 49, Folder 27)
- Shepard, Charles H. - Property, 1957-1958 (Box 49, Folder 30)
- Sherman, W. H. (see Zinola), 1950-1952 (Box 49, Folder 31)
- Shopping Center - Expansion - Joseph Magnin & Blum’s, 1960-1962 (Box 58, Folder 17)
- Shopping Center - Expansion - Parking & Malls Architect, 1960-1973 (Box 58, Folder 18)
- Shopping Center - Expansion 1961 - Parking & Malls - Construction (Box 59, Folder 2)
- Shopping Center - General (5), 1969-1971 (Box 58, Folder 20)
- Shopping Center - General Exhibits (Box 58, Folder 19)
- Shopping Center - Landscaping, 1955-1972 (Box 59, Folder 1)
- Shopping Center - Renovation/Expansion Studies - Correspondence (Rouse, John Thompson, CBMC), 1972-1975 (Box 59, Folder 3)
- Shopping Center, 1970-1973 (Box 100, Folder 4)
- Shoup, Jack W., 1941-1956 (Box 49, Folder 32)
- Sigma Alpha Epsilon I, 1945-1955 (Box 80, Folder 1)
- Sigma Alpha Epsilon II, 1956-1962 (Box 80, Folder 2)
- Sigma Alpha Epsilon, 1927-1939 (Box 49, Folder 33)
- Sigma Alpha Epsilon, 1938-1945 (Box 49, Folder 34)
- Sigma Chi #1, 1938-1963 (Box 80, Folder 3)
- Sigma Chi Fraternity, 1936-1938 (Box 80, Folder 4)
- Sigma Nu, 1955-1963 (Box 80, Folder 5)
- Signatures Authorized, 1965-1968 (Box 63, Folder 16)
- Signatures Authorized, Folder 1, 1937-1958 (Box 80, Folder 18)
- Signatures Authorized, Folder 2, 1960-1965 (Box 64, Folder 1)
- Skidmore, Owings & Merrill - Commercial Area - L.D., 1953 (Box 80, Folder 10)
- Skidmore, Owings & Merrill - Conferences, 1953 (Box 80, Folder 7)
- Skidmore, Owings & Merrill - Contracts & Payments, 1953-1957 (Box 80, Folder 8)
- Skidmore, Owings & Merrill - Industrial Area, 1953-1955 (Box 80, Folder 11)
- Skidmore, Owings & Merrill - Job Memorandums, 1953-1954 (Box 80, Folder 12)
- Skidmore, Owings & Merrill - Job Memorandums, 1954 (Box 80, Folder 9)
- Skidmore, Owings & Merrill - Master Plan Distribution, 1954-1961 (Box 80, Folder 13)
- Skidmore, Owings & Merrill - Professional Area, 1954 (Box 80, Folder 14)
- Skidmore, Owings & Merrill - Reports, 1953-1954 (Box 80, Folder 15)
- Skidmore, Owings & Merrill, 1952-1959 (Box 80, Folder 6)
- Slenderella Systems - Correspondence, 1955-1963 (Box 80, Folder 16)
- Slenderella Systems - Lease, 1955-1957 (Box 80, Folder 17)
- Smith, Mrs. E. W. (May Hurlbut Smith), 1934-1964 (Box 80, Folder 19)
- Smoking, 1934-1968 (Box 59, Folder 4)
- Soares, Edward Joseph & Margaret Loeb, 1949-1951 (Box 80, Folder 20)
- Social Security - Federal & State, 1940-1953 (Box 80, Folder 21)
- Society of Hospital Attorneys, 1969-1970 (Box 59, Folder 5)
- Soil Investigation - Clyde Woodward & Assoc., 1954 Report (Box 59, Folder 6)
- Soil Investigation Report, 1956-1958 (Box 39, Folder 7)
- Soils of the Campus, 1944-1966 (Box 59, Folder 7)
- Solar Telescope Mounting Structure - Affirmative Action Program, 737 (empty folder) (Box 106, Folder 28)
- Solar Telescope Mounting Structure - Affirmative Action Reports, 737, 1973-1974 (Box 106, Folder 31)
- Solar Telescope Mounting Structure - Budget & Fiscal, 737, 1973-1975 (Box 106, Folder 35)
- Solar Telescope Mounting Structure - Bulletins & Supplements, 737, 1973-1974 (Box 106, Folder 32)
- Solar Telescope Mounting Structure - Contract Changes, 737, 1973-1974 (Box 106, Folder 30)
- Solar Telescope Mounting Structure - Correspondence, 1973-1975 (Box 106, Folder 26)
- Solar Telescope Mounting Structure - Disbursements, 737, 1973-1975 (Box 106, Folder 33)
- Solar Telescope Mounting Structure - Exhibits, 737, 1973 (Box 106, Folder 36)
- Solar Telescope Mounting Structure - Field Inspectors Progress Reports, 737, 1973-1974 (Box 106, Folder 34)
- Solar Telescope Mounting Structure - Legal, 737, 1973-1974 (Box 106, Folder 29)
- Solar Telescope Mounting Structure - Testing Laboratory Reports, 737, 1973-1974 (Box 106, Folder 27)
- Sororities - Appraisals, 1944-1945 (Box 80, Folder 22)
- Sororities - Purchased by University, 1943-1945 (Box 80, Folder 23)
- Southern Pacific - 1892-1976 (Box 59, Folder 8)
- Sowards, G. Wesley, 1962-1968 (Box 80, Folder 24)
- Space - Allotment of Rooms & Bldg. area to Academic & Admin. Departments I, 1959-1963 (Box 80, Folder 25)
- Space - Allotment of Rooms & Bldg. area to Academic & Admin. Depts. 2, 1963-1969 (Box 59, Folder 10)
- Space - Allotment of Rooms & Bldg. area to Academic & Admin. Depts. 3, 1969-1971 (Box 59, Folder 9)
- Space - Old Corporation Yard Area, 1968 (Box 59, Folder 12)
- Space Engineering - Legal, 1964-1969 (Box 102, Folder 5)
- Space Engineering Building, 1967 (Box 59, Folder 11)
- Sparks, Marshall S. Jr., 1963-1968 (Box 80, Folder 26)
- Spencer, E.T. - Director of Planning, 1948-1956 (Box 80, Folder 27)
- SRI International, 1972-1975 (Box 98, Folder 5)
- SSC - Budget, 1975 (Box 33, Folder 52)
- SSC Leasing Summary Status Report, 1977-1978 (Box 33, Folder 25)
- SSC Sq. Footage, 1976-1977 (Box 33, Folder 28)
- Stadium Improvements - Budget & Fiscal, 1972-1973 (Box 111, Folder 7)
- Stadium Improvements - Bulletins, Supplements, 1973 (Box 111, Folder 11)
- Stadium Improvements - Contract Changes, 1973 (Box 111, Folder 10)
- Stadium Improvements - Disbursements, 1972-1973 (Box 111, Folder 6)
- Stadium Improvements - Field Inspector’s Progress Report, 1973 (Box 111, Folder 13)
- Stadium Improvements - General Correspondence, 1972-1974 (Box 111, Folder 9)
- Stadium Improvements - Job Site Meetings, 1973 (Box 111, Folder 12)
- Stadium Improvements - Legal, 1972-1973 (Box 111, Folder 8)
- Stadium Improvements - Testing Lab. Reports, 1972 (Box 111, Folder 14)
- Stadium Seat Repairs - Legal Documents, 1963 (Box 102, Folder 9)
- Standard Oil Co. (Campus) Physical Plant, 1961-1963 (Box 59, Folder 13)
- Stanford Bookstore-Post Office Constr. - Exhibits, 1956-1960 (Box 102, Folder 25)
- Stanford Campus Homeowners Association, 1967-1974 (Box 59, Folder 14)
- Stanford Convalescent Home - Correspondence, 1933-1960 (Box 80, Folder 28)
- Stanford Hospital - Proposed Medical Office Bldg. - Clay & Webster, 1956-1957 (Box 59, Folder 15)
- Stanford Hospital Elevator - San Francisco - General, 1951-1965 (Box 80, Folder 31)
- Stanford Hospital Elevator - San Francisco, 1956-1959 (Box 80, Folder 30)
- Stanford Hospital Re-Zoning, 1955-1956 (Box 80, Folder 29)
- Stanford Linear Accelerator Center - Architectural Planning (after Luckman Assoc.), 1966-1968 (Box 59, Folder 21)
- Stanford Linear Accelerator Center - Construction & Design: Standards, 1961-1967 (Box 59, Folder 17)
- Stanford Linear Accelerator Center - Contract AT (04-3) - 400 Document, 1961-1962 (Box 63, Folder 15)
- Stanford Linear Accelerator Center - County Permit, 1961-1962 (Box 59, Folder 18)
- Stanford Linear Accelerator Center - Freeway Crossing - Right of Entry, 1961-1968 (Box 59, Folder 19)
- Stanford Linear Accelerator Center - Indemnification, 1960-1974 (Box 59, Folder 20)
- Stanford Linear Accelerator Center - Labor Relations - Folder III, 1965-1969 (Box 59, Folder 22)
- Stanford Linear Accelerator Center - Negotiating Committee, 1961-1962 (Box 63, Folder 14)
- Stanford Linear Accelerator Center - PG&E Contract (with AEC) for Natural Gas - Correspondence & Document AT(04-3)-484, 1962-1963 (Box 59, Folder 23)
- Stanford Linear Accelerator Center - Roads, 1961-1971 (Box 59, Folder 24)
- Stanford Linear Accelerator Center - Sand Hill Construction Plans - Approval Records, #1, 1962-1967 (Box 60, Folder 1)
- Stanford Linear Accelerator Center - Sand Hill Construction Plans - Approval Records, #2, 1966-1971 (Box 60, Folder 2)
- Stanford Linear Accelerator Center - Water & Sewers, 1962-1966 (Box 60, Folder 3)
- Stanford Linear Accelerator Center Cafeteria, 1963-1969 (Box 59, Folder 16)
- Stanford Linear Accelerator Center, 1975 (Box 99, Folder 26)
- Stanford Overseas - Germany - General, Folder #1, 1957-1959 (Box 81, Folder 1)
- Stanford Overseas - Transportation for 1958 and 1959 (Box 81, Folder 3)
- Stanford Overseas - Transportation for 1960 (Box 81, Folder 4)
- Stanford Overseas - Transportation for 1961 (Box 81, Folder 5)
- Stanford Overseas Graduate/ Special Programs - Alpbach, NDEA Institute of American History in Austria, 1965-1967 (Box 81, Folder 2)
- Stanford Red, 1955 (Box 81, Folder 6)
- Stanford Research Institute - Documents, 1946-1970 (Box 60, Folder 4)
- Stanford Research Institute - Economic Survey, 1953-1955 (Box 81, Folder 7)
- Stanford Shopping Center Management Procedures Manual, 1977 (Binder) (Box 33)
- Stanford Shopping Centert - Management Information System - Computer Overview, 1978 (Box 33)
- Stanford Solid Waste Energy Program, 1977 (Box 92, Folder 8)
- Stanford Solid Waste Energy Program, 1977-1978 (Box 92, Folder 10)
- Stanford Solid Waste Energy Program, 1978-1979 (Box 92, Folder 9)
- Stanford Solid Waste, 1977 (Box 92, Folder 7)
- Stanford Union, 1958-1962 (Box 81, Folder 8)
- Stanford Village - (Yearly) Audits, 1951-1954 (Box 81, Folder 9)
- Stanford Village - Barber Shop, 1946-1964 (Box 81, Folder 10)
- Stanford Village - Blueprint Plans, Thomas & Whipple, 1946-1947 (Box 81, Folder 11)
- Stanford Village - Budgets, Revised, 1955-1956 (Box 81, Folder 12)
- Stanford Village - Buildings and Grounds, 1947-1965 (Box 81, Folder 13)
- Stanford Village - Capacity, 1946-1947 (Box 81, Folder 14)
- Stanford Village - Circulars - PHA Field Office, 1947-1951 (Box 81, Folder 15)
- Stanford Village - Civil Defense, 1950-1952 (Box 81, Folder 16)
- Stanford Village - Commissary #1, 1946-1956 (Box 81, Folder 17)
- Stanford Village - Commissary Price Lists, 1950-1966 (Box 81, Folder 18)
- Stanford Village - Consolidation (Possible)1946-1947 (Box 81, Folder 19)
- Stanford Village - Contracts - PHA, 1946-1948 (Box 81, Folder 20)
- Stanford Village - Correspondence, Disposition of Property, CAL-V-4376 and CAL-VN-4577, 1948-1954 (Box 81, Folder 21)
- Stanford Village - Disposition of Property, 1955-1956 (Box 81, Folder 22)
- Stanford Village - Dormitories, 1947-1964 (Box 81, Folder 23)
- Stanford Village - Family Council Minutes, 1957-1961 (Box 81, Folder 24)
- Stanford Village - Federal Works Agency, 1946-1947 (Box 81, Folder 25)
- Stanford Village - Floor Area (Box 81, Folder 26)
- Stanford Village - Furniture and Equipment, 1946-1957 (Box 81, Folder 27)
- Stanford Village - Housing Forms, 1947-1949 (Box 81, Folder 29)
- Stanford Village - Housing, 1946-1963 (Box 81, Folder 28)
- Stanford Village - In-Quota HA(V-4376), 1946-1955 (Box 81, Folder 30)
- Stanford Village - Insurance - Instructions for handling personal insurance of students located in Stanford Village, 1947-1949 (Box 81, Folder 31)
- Stanford Village - Laundry, 1946-1963 (Box 81, Folder 32)
- Stanford Village - Legal, Correspondence with Attorneys, 1950-1955 (Box 81, Folder 33)
- Stanford Village - Nursery School, Stanford University, 1947-1956 (Box 81, Folder 34)
- Stanford Village - O.P.A., 1946 (Box 81, Folder 35)
- Stanford Village - Occupancy Reports, 1946-1961 (Box 82, Folder 1)
- Stanford Village - Out of Quota, CAL-VN-4577, 1946-1955 (Box 82, Folder 2)
- Stanford Village - Pacific Telecoin (Bendix), 1946-1953 (Box 82, Folder 4)
- Stanford Village - PHA - Equipment List, 1947 (Box 82, Folder 3)
- Stanford Village - Project Management Plan - Budget 1947-1948 Est. Annual Income & Expense (Box 82, Folder 7)
- Stanford Village - Project Management Plan - Correspondence, 1946-1952 (Box 82, Folder 6)
- Stanford Village - Project Management Plan - Supporting Detail (Box 82, Folder 5)
- Stanford Village - Project Management Plan, 1948-1949 (Box 82, Folder 8)
- Stanford Village - Project Management Plan, 1952 (Box 82, Folder 9)
- Stanford Village - Project Reports, 1946-1947 (Box 82, Folder 10)
- Stanford Village - Public Housing Authority, 1946-1957 (Box 82, Folder 11)
- Stanford Village - Public Relations, 1946-1955 (Box 82, Folder 12)
- Stanford Village - Rents, 1946-1955 (Box 82, Folder 13)
- Stanford Village - Sanitation, 1946-1958 (Box 82, Folder 14)
- Stanford Village - Traffic Signal - Ravenswood & El Camino, 1946-1949 (Box 82, Folder 15)
- Stanford Village - Transfer and Reimbursable Development Costs, 1950-1953 (Box 82, Folder 17)
- Stanford Village - Transportation, 1946-1960 (Box 82, Folder 16)
- Stanford Village - Trees, Removal of, 1947 (Box 82, Folder 18)
- Stanford Village - Union Negotiations, 1946-1948 (Box 82, Folder 19)
- Stanford Village - Wage Survey, 1952-1955 (Box 82, Folder 20)
- Stanford Village - War Assets Adm., 1946-1949 (Box 82, Folder 21)
- Stanford Weekend Acres (North & South) - Rural Lane, Happy Hollow Lane, etc., #2, 1936-1959 (Box 60, Folder 6)
- Stanford Weekend Acres (North & South) - Rural Lane, Happy Hollow Lane, etc., #2, 1960-1969 (Box 60, Folder 5)
- Stanford Women's Club, 1933-1970 (Box 60, Folder 7)
- Stanford/ Palo Alto Relations - Seman Report, 1973-1975 (Box 97, Folder 4)
- Stanford/Palo Alto Relations, 1972-1975 (Box 97, Folder 2)
- Status Report - SSC, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 23)
- Stauffer I & II - Exterior Tile Repair, 781, 1969-1975 (Box 103, Folder 35)
- Stauffer II - Legal Documents, 1962-1964 (Thomas Church, Landscape Architect) (Box 102, Folder 8)
- Stauffer III, Rm. 109 Alterations, 708, File I, 1972-1973 (Box 105, Folder 8)
- Stauffer III, Room 006 - Laboratory Alterations, 698, 1972-1973 (Box 104, Folder 14)
- Steel - gift of Property, 1953-1954 (Box 82, Folder 22)
- Steele, Jack, 1965-1968 (Box 82, Folder 23)
- Steere, Wm. C. & Dorothy O., 1949-1958 (Box 82, Folder 24)
- Stein, Max. H., Estate of, Los Angeles Property, 1959-1961 (Box 82, Folder 25)